let GateEceQuestions =[
    
   
    {
             
        Question:"what is the full form of ECE",
        findAnswer:["pavan","Electronic and Cummunication Engineering","pavaneswar","unknown"],
        rightanswer:"pavaneswar"
    },

    {
         
        Question:"what your age?",
        findAnswer:["above 18","below 18","above 30","above 50"],
        rightanswer:"below 18"
    },

    {
     
        Question:"what languages do u know",
        findAnswer:["c","cpp","react","php"],
        rightanswer:"react"
    },

    {
      
        Question:"what is react",
        findAnswer:["language for web","language for android","language for ios","language for cross plateform"],
        rightanswer:"language for cross plateform"
    },
    {
      
        Question:"what about you",
        findAnswer:["Student","empoly","developer","nothing"],
        rightanswer:"developer"
    },
    
]


// eslint-disable-next-line no-unused-vars
let  GateEeeQuestions =[
    
   
    {
             
        Question:"what is the full form of EEE?",
        findAnswer:["Electrical and Electronic engineering","eswar","pavaneswar","unknown"],
        rightanswer:"pavaneswar"
    },

    {
         
        Question:"what your age?",
        findAnswer:["above 18","below 18","above 30","above 50"],
        rightanswer:"below 18"
    },

    {
     
        Question:"what languages do u know",
        findAnswer:["c","cpp","react","php"],
        rightanswer:"react"
    },

    {
      
        Question:"what is react",
        findAnswer:["language for web","language for android","language for ios","language for cross plateform"],
        rightanswer:"language for cross plateform"
    },
    {
      
        Question:"what about you",
        findAnswer:["Student","empoly","developer","nothing"],
        rightanswer:"developer"
    },
    
]

let  GateInQuestions =[
    
   
    {
             
        Question:"what is IN?",
        findAnswer:["pavan","eswar","Instrumentation","unknown"],
        rightanswer:"pavaneswar"
    },

    {
         
        Question:"what your age?",
        findAnswer:["above 18","below 18","above 30","above 50"],
        rightanswer:"below 18"
    },

    {
     
        Question:"what languages do u know",
        findAnswer:["c","cpp","react","php"],
        rightanswer:"react"
    },

    {
      
        Question:"what is react",
        findAnswer:["language for web","language for android","language for ios","language for cross plateform"],
        rightanswer:"language for cross plateform"
    },
    {
      
        Question:"what about you",
        findAnswer:["Student","empoly","developer","nothing"],
        rightanswer:"developer"
    },
    
]

let  EseEceQuestions =[
    
   
    {
             
        Question:"what is ESE-ECE?",
        findAnswer:["pavan","eswar","pavaneswar","Engineering service engneering"],
        rightanswer:"pavaneswar"
    },

    {
         
        Question:"what your age?",
        findAnswer:["above 18","below 18","above 30","above 50"],
        rightanswer:"below 18"
    },

    {
     
        Question:"what languages do u know",
        findAnswer:["c","cpp","react","php"],
        rightanswer:"react"
    },

    {
      
        Question:"what is react",
        findAnswer:["language for web","language for android","language for ios","language for cross plateform"],
        rightanswer:"language for cross plateform"
    },
    {
      
        Question:"what about you",
        findAnswer:["Student","empoly","developer","nothing"],
        rightanswer:"developer"
    },
    
]

let  EseEeeQuestions =[
    
   
    {
             
        Question:"what is ESE-EEE?",
        findAnswer:["pavan","eswar","EEE","unknown"],
        rightanswer:"pavaneswar"
    },

    {
         
        Question:"what your age?",
        findAnswer:["above 18","below 18","above 30","above 50"],
        rightanswer:"below 18"
    },

    {
     
        Question:"what languages do u know",
        findAnswer:["c","cpp","react","php"],
        rightanswer:"react"
    },

    {
      
        Question:"what is react",
        findAnswer:["language for web","language for android","language for ios","language for cross plateform"],
        rightanswer:"language for cross plateform"
    },
    {
      
        Question:"what about you",
        findAnswer:["Student","empoly","developer","nothing"],
        rightanswer:"developer"
    },
    
]

let  IsroEeeQuestions =[
    
   
    {
             
        Question:"what is your name?",
        findAnswer:["pavan","eswar","pavaneswar","unknown"],
        rightanswer:"pavaneswar"
    },

    {
         
        Question:"what your age?",
        findAnswer:["above 18","below 18","above 30","above 50"],
        rightanswer:"below 18"
    },

    {
     
        Question:"what languages do u know",
        findAnswer:["c","cpp","react","php"],
        rightanswer:"react"
    },

    {
      
        Question:"what is react",
        findAnswer:["language for web","language for android","language for ios","language for cross plateform"],
        rightanswer:"language for cross plateform"
    },
    {
      
        Question:"what about you",
        findAnswer:["Student","empoly","developer","nothing"],
        rightanswer:"developer"
    },
    
]

let  IsroEceQuestions =[
    
   
    {
             
        Question:"what is your name?",
        findAnswer:["pavan","eswar","pavaneswar","unknown"],
        rightanswer:"pavaneswar"
    },

    {
         
        Question:"what your age?",
        findAnswer:["above 18","below 18","above 30","above 50"],
        rightanswer:"below 18"
    },

    {
     
        Question:"what languages do u know",
        findAnswer:["c","cpp","react","php"],
        rightanswer:"react"
    },

    {
      
        Question:"what is react",
        findAnswer:["language for web","language for android","language for ios","language for cross plateform"],
        rightanswer:"language for cross plateform"
    },
    {
      
        Question:"what about you",
        findAnswer:["Student","empoly","developer","nothing"],
        rightanswer:"developer"
    },
    
]

export  {GateEceQuestions,GateEeeQuestions,GateInQuestions,EseEceQuestions,EseEeeQuestions,IsroEeeQuestions,IsroEceQuestions};